MIYU SETOYAMA

Frontend Developer

PROFILE

Passionate Frontend Developer who loves creating new things. Expert knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React. Familiar with Full Stack development, particularly the MERN stack. I am excellent in teamwork and enjoy collaboration with peers; Also, I am confident in the development of front-end for e-commerce sites and the creation of modern interfaces.

EXPERIENCES

Full-Stack Web Developer & Data Entry

Unitec Japan, Japan / Jul 2020 - Current

- · Consult with the client on web and software requirements for their business
- Redesign existing websites to improve performance by up to 50% at a time
- · Create the company website, using Nextjs, React, React Redux, Nodejs, Express, Mongodb, and GraphQL
- Support software throughout the entire development lifecycle. Including proof of concept, system testing, fixing bugs, performance tuning and production support

Retail & Wholesale Buyer

Branches & Knots Trading Co. Ltd., Vancouver / Oct 2016 - Mar 2020

- Helped grow sales by 20% every year through management of planning, production and buying for all brands and sales channels
- · Review requirement of establish and determine quality and type of merchandise to purchase
- Study market reports, trade periodicals and sales promotion materials and visit trade shows, showrooms, factories and product design event

EDUCATION

Web And Mobile App Development Diploma

Cornerstone International Community College Of Canada - Vancouver, BC / Sep 2020 - Aug 2021

- Acquired front-end skills such as HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, React, React Hooks, Redux, Next.js, and TypeScript
- · Acquired back-end skills such as Java, Node, Express, Python, MySQL, PostgreSQL, and MongoDB
- · Deployed websites and applications using GitHub, Netlify, Heroku, and Firebase
- · Collaborated and worked in a team environment using Git, GitHub, and Jira

Forum for International Trade Training (FITT) Diploma

Canadian College - Vancouver, BC / Dec 2015 - Dec 2016

- · Creating marketing and research plans
- · Developing marketing, financing, management and legal skills

SKILLS

LANGUAGES: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Python, ReactJS, Redux, NextJS, NodeJS, Tailwind CSS, SASS, BootStrap, Material UI, Express, Django

SYSTEMS & DATABASES: MongoDB, Git, GraphQL, Insomnia, Figma, Jira